Guide to the Johan Kugelberg punk collection, circa 1974-1986.
Kugelberg, Johan punk collection
- Series II. Fliers and Posters
  - Weirdos, The, 1984; 8.5 x 5.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 26)
    Venue: Whisky a Go Go and The Vex
    Additional bands or artists: Mad Society, Sexsick
    Main text: Weirdos with the Crowd and Legal Weapon - Fri. Feb. 13th - Vex
  - Weirdos, The, 8.5 x 5.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 26)
    Additional bands or artists: The Plugz, Gears
    Main text: Weirdos, Plugz, Gears …
  - Weirdos, The, 11 x 17 in. (Box 27, Folder 3)
    Main text: The Weirdos go-ga-ga at the Whiskey A-Go-Go
  - Wire, 1977; 7.5 x 22 in. (Box 30, Folder 2)
    Main text: Wire - Their album Pink Flag out now
  - Xmen, 1982; 8.5 x 5.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 26)
    Additional bands or artists: Conservatives, Suspex, Monickers, Agents
    Main text: Xmen and Conservatives with Suspex plus Monickers & Agents
  - Youth Brigade, 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 26)
    Additional bands or artists: Channel 3, 7 Seconds, Stretch Marks, Rigor Mortis
    Main text: Goldenvoice in co-ordination with Better Youth Organization presents Something To Believe In - A 4th of July celebration with Youth Brigade …
  - Youth Brigade, 1979; 8.5 x 5.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 26)
    Additional bands or artists: Rigor Mortis, Tourists, Burgalurs
    Main text: Get your stompin boots on and head on down for some rip-roarin sing-a-long kinda o fun … with Youth Brigade …
  - Youth Brigade, 1986; 8.5 x 5.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 26)
    Additional bands or artists: The Weirdos, Faith No More, Junior Gone Wild
    Main text: After 7 months in hiding - Babble-On presents… Youth Brigade - w/special guests in a rare performance …
  - Youth in Asia, 1983; 8.5 x 5.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 26)
    Artist: Mark
    Location: n.p. [UK?]
    Main text: A Christian publication - youthinAsia
    Notes: General promotional flier.
  - Zeros, The, 1980s; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 26)
    Additional bands or artists: The Cosmetics, The Vandals, The Conservatives
    Main text: Zeros - The Cosmetics …
  - Zeros, The, 1983; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 26)
    Venue: Adams Ave. Theatre
    Additional bands or artists: The Hitmakers
    Main text: You are invited to attend the San Diego new wave rock & roll showcase featuring the Zeros …
- Series III. Newspapers
  - Miscellaneous newspapers (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous A, I (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous R-S (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Oasis d'Neon (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - X Magazine (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Amos Poe's Autograph, May, 1977; Issue #: 1; 16.5 x 11.5 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Notes: Full title: Amos Poe's Autograph
  - Andy Warhol's Interview, January, 1973; Issue #: 29; 15 x 11.5 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Editors: Andy Warhol, Paul Morrissey, Fred Hughes
  - Andy Warhol's Interview, March, 1973; Issue #: 30; 15 x 11.5 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Notes: Lou Reed interview
  - Andy Warhol's Interview, January, 1975; Volume #: 5, Issue #: 1; 15.5x11.5 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Editors: Bob Colacello
  - Aquarian Night Owl: Everynight Charley, 1978; Issue #: 199; 15 x 11.5 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    Publication location: Montclair, NJ, United States
    Editors: James Rensenbrink
    Notes: Cover story on Sex Pistols US tour. Supplement to the Aquarian Weekly
  - Aquarian Weekly, July, 1977; Volume #: 12, Issue #: 167; 15 x 11.5 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Aylesbury Roxette, December, 1976; Issue #: 5; 18 x 12.25 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    Publication location: Aylesbury, Buckinghamshire, Great Britain
    Editors: Chris France
  - Burning River News, February 6, 1970; Volume #: 3, Issue #: 6; 15x11 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    Notes: Bob Rolontz (addressed to)
  - Cassette Gazzette, 1984; Issue #: 8; 16.5 x 11.5 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Cle, 1977; Issue #: [2]; 14.5 x 11.5 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Comical Funnies, 1980-1981; Issue #: 1-3; 17 x 11.5 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    Editors: Petter Bagge, John Holmstrom
  - Crawdaddy, 1970; Volume #: 4, Issue #: 2; 17 x 11.5 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    Editors: Peter Stafford
    Notes: In two sections (bagged together).
  - Damage, July, 1979; Volume #: 1, Issue #: 1; 11.5x17.5 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    Editors: Brad L.
  - Damage, 1980; Volume #: 1, Issue #: 5; 11.5x17.5 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Damage, September, 1980; Volume #: 1, Issue #: 10; 11.5x17.5 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Damage, December, 1980; Volume #: 1, Issue #: 11; 11.5x17.5 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Disc, 8-12-1972; 16.5x12 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - East Village Eye, June, 1980; Volume #: 2, Issue #: 12; 11x17 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    Editors: Leonard Abrams
    Major contributors: "The Death of Punk" cover story (on Punk Magazine)
  - East Village Eye, April, 1983; Volume #: 5, Issue #: 31; 11x17 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - East Village Other, February 8, 1968; Volume #: 3, Issue #: 9; 17 x 11.5 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - East Village Other, April 19, 1968; Volume #: 3, Issue #: 20; 17 x 11.5 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - East Village Other, June 28, 1968; Volume #: 3, Issue #: 30; 17 x 11.5 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - East Village Other, July 19, 1968; Volume #: 3, Issue #: 32; 17 x 11.5 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - East Village Other, August 16, 1968; Volume #: 3, Issue #: 37; 17 x 11.5 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - East Village Other, March 19, 1969; Volume #: 4, Issue #: 16; 17 x 11.5 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    Notes: Henry Sobotka (addressed to)
  - East Village Other, July 23, 1969; Volume #: 4, Issue #: 34; 17 x 11.5 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - East Village Other, November 19, 1969; Volume #: 4, Issue #: 51; 17 x 11.5 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - East Village Other, December 10, 1969; Volume #: 5, Issue #: 1; 17 x 11.5 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - East Village Other, February 18, 1970; Volume #: 5, Issue #: 11; 17 x 11.5 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - East Village Other, February 25, 1970; Volume #: 5, Issue #: 12; 17 x 11.5 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - East Village Other, April 14, 1970; Volume #: 5, Issue #: 20; 17 x 11.5 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - East Village Other, June 9, 1970; Volume #: 5, Issue #: 28; 17 x 11.5 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Fusion, October 3, 1969; 11x17.5 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    Publication location: Boston, MA, United States
    Editors: Robert Somma
  - Fusion, February 6, 1970; Issue #: 26; 11x17.5 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Fusion, March 20, 1970; Issue #: 29; 11x17.5 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Fusion, June 8, 1970; Issue #: 34; 11x17.5 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Fusion, June 12, 1970; Issue #: 35; 11x17.5 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Fusion, July 10, 1970; Issue #: 37; 11x17.5 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    Editors: Robbert Somma
    Major contributors: Nick Tosches
    Notes: Cover story: "The Punk Muse" by Nick Tosches
  - Gig, January 1978; Volume #: 4, Issue #: 5; 15 x 11.75 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    Editors: Sam Chase, Jean-Charles Costa
    Major contributors: Lester Bangs
    Notes: Richard Hell story by Lester Bangs
  - Gulcher, 1975; Issue #: 0; 11x16 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    Editors: Bob Richert
  - Gulcher, 1975; Issue #: 1; 11x16 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    Notes: Promotional sample issue with cover letter and three issues of the related music calendar "Gulchin'!" (#s 7, 8, 9, and 10, dated Sept. 1 through Oct. 13, 1975).
  - Gulcher, 1976; Issue #: 2; 11x16 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Gulcher, 1976; Issue #: 3; 11x16 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Gulcher, 1976-Summer; Issue #: 4; 11x16 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Gulcher, 1976-Fall; Issue #: 5; 11x16 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Gulcher, 1977-Fall; Issue #: 6; 11x16 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - IT: International Times, 1979; Volume #: 6, Issue #: 2; 16.5 x 12.5 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    Notes: Punk reviews
  - Melody Maker, March 26, 1977; 18 x 13.5 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    Editors: Ray Coleman
    Major contributors: Catherine Coon
    Notes: Cover story on A&M dropping Sex Pistols. Tape repair to spine.
  - Melody Maker, June 4, 1977; 18 x 13.5 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    Notes: Cover story Sex Pistols. Tape repair to spine.
  - Melody Maker, July 9, 1977; 18 x 13.5 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Melody Maker, August 20, 1977; 18 x 13.5 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    Notes: Cover story Sex Pistols "guerilla tour"; story on Desperate Bicycles/DIY. Tape repair to spine.
  - Melody Maker, December 10, 1977; 18 x 13.5 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    Notes: Cover story on Sex Pistols. Tape repair to spine.
  - Modern Review, 1991-Fall; Volume #: 1, Issue #: 1; 16.5 x 11.5 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    Editors: Toby Young
    Major contributors: Julie Burchill
    Notes: Review of England's Dreaming
  - Muziekkrant OOR, July 26, 1978; Issue #: 15; 23 x 18, folded to 11.5 x 18 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    Publication location:, Netherlands
    Notes: In two sections.
  - New Musical Express, December 11, 1976; 17 x 12 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    Notes: Cover story on Sex Pistols/Grundy scandal
  - New Wave (USA), 1977; 15x11.5 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    Editors: Howie Klein, Steve Seid
  - New York Daily Press, October 13, 1978; Volume #: 1, Issue #: 45; 15 x 11.5 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    Notes: Article on murder of Nancy Spungeon
  - New York News Magazine, September 19, 1976; 12.5 x 11 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    Editors: Richard C. Lemon
    Notes: Cover story on punk
  - New York Rocker, 1976; Issue #: 1-7, 9-10; 11x17 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - New York Rocker, 1976; Issue #: 2; 11x17 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - New York Rocker, 1976; Issue #: 3; 11x17 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    Editors: Craig Gholson, Guillemette Barbet
  - New York Rocker, 1976; Issue #: 4; 11x17 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    Editors: Craig Gholson
  - New York Rocker, 1976; Issue #: 5; 11x17 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - New York Rocker, 1977; Issue #: 6; 11x17 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - New York Rocker, 1977; Issue #: 7; 11x17 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - New York Rocker, 1977; Issue #: 9; 11x17 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - New York Rocker, 1977; Issue #: 10; 11x17 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - New York Rocker, 1978; Issue #: 13; 11x17 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    Editors: Andrew Schwartz
  - New York Rocker, 1978; Issue #: 14; 11x17 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - New York Rocker, 1978; Issue #: 15; 11x17 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - New York Rocker, 1979; Issue #: 21; 11x17 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - New York Rocker, 1979; Issue #: 22; 11x17 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - New York Rocker, 1979; Issue #: 24; 11x17 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - New York Rocker, 1980; Issue #: 26; 11x17 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    Notes: Cover title: NY Rocker
  - New York Rocker, 1980; Issue #: nn; 11x17 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - New York Rocker, 1981; Issue #: nn; 11x17 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - New York Rocker, 1981; Issue #: 42; 11x17 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    Notes: Cover title: NY Rocker. p. 15-25 are a "Slash extra"-- a special supplement by the editors of the LA fanzine Slash.
  - New York Rocker, 1981; Issue #: 44; 11x17 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Newsday, January 25, 1976; 15 x 11.5 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    Publication location:, United States
    Notes: Article "Punk rock: its day will come". Pages 1-6 and 55-60 of part 2 only, containing the punk article.
  - No Magazine, 1978?; Volume #: 1, Issue #: 7; 11x17 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Publication location: Edgecliff, NSW, Australia
    Notes: Continues from Spurt; cover title: Spurt! [crossed out] No
  - OP, 1980-Fall; Issue #: C; 17.5 x 11.5 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - OP, 1980-Winter; Issue #: D; 17.5 x 11.5 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    Notes: Wasp Records (addressed to). Issues are lettered rather than numbered; each issue covers bands beginning with the theme letter.
  - OP, 1981-Spring; Issue #: E; 17.5 x 11.5 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - OP, January, 1982; Issue #: I; 17.5 x 11.5 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Orcano, Issue #: 0; 49 x 35 cm., folded to 35 x 24.5 cm. (Box 15, Folder 6)
    Publication location: Enschede, Netherlands
    Editors: P. Hajenius
    Notes: Official publication of 1000 Idioten Records
  - Poster, November, 1977; Volume #: 3, Issue #: 11; 42 x 29 cm. (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Poster, January, 1978; Volume #: 4, Issue #: 1; 42 x 29 cm. (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Poster, February, 1978; Volume #: 4, Issue #: 2; 42 x 29 cm. (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Poster, March, 1978]; Volume #: 4, Issue #: 3; 42 x 29 cm. (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Primotimes, February 23, 1976; Issue #: 45; 11x17 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    Editors: Vic Bracht, Michael Redman, Bob Slone
    Notes: Article on the fanzine Gulcher
  - Psyclone, 1977; Volume #: 2, Issue #: 1; 11x17 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    Editors: Jerry Paulsen
    Major contributors: Howie Klein
    Notes: Punk article by Jack Badger, pen name for Howie Klein
  - Radio Free Hollywood, 1977; Issue #: 2; 11.5x14.5 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    Publication location: Wilcox Station, CA, United States
    Editors: Allan Rinde
  - Re/Search, 1981; Issue #: 2; 17.5 x 11.5 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    Editors: Vale
  - Re/Search, 1981; Issue #: 3; 17.5 x 11.5 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Rock, 1970; Volume #: 2, Issue #: 11; 11x17 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    Editors: Larry Marshak
    Major contributors: Patti Smith
    Notes: Patti Smith's first published writing.
  - Rock Scene Backstage Scrapbook, 1977; Issue #: 1; 17 x 11.5 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    Publication location: Bethany, CT, United States
  - Rolling Stone, October 20, 1977; Issue #: 250; 14 x 11.5 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    Editors: Jann S. Wenner
  - Rotten, 1970?; Issue #: 1; 40 x 29 cm. (Box 16, Folder 5)
    Publication location: København, Denmark
    Editors: Jan Michaelson
  - Rotten, 1970; Issue #: 2; 40 x 29 cm. (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Search and Destroy, 1977; Issue #: 1; 11.5x17.5 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Search and Destroy, 1977; Issue #: 2; 11.5x17.5 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Search and Destroy, 1977; Issue #: 3; 11.5x17.5 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Search and Destroy, 1977; Issue #: 4; 11.5x17.5 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Search and Destroy, 1978; Issue #: 5; 11.5x17.5 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Search and Destroy, 1978; Issue #: 6; 11.5x17.5 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Search and Destroy, 1978; Issue #: 7; 11.5x17.5 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Search and Destroy, 1978; Issue #: 8; 11.5x17.5 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Search and Destroy, 1978; Issue #: 9; 11.5x17.5 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Search and Destroy, 1978; Issue #: 10; 11.5x17.5 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Search and Destroy, 1979; Volume #: 2, Issue #: 11; 11.5x17.5 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Shades, 1979; Issue #: 4; 11x17 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    Editors: George Dot Higton, Sheila Wawanash
  - Slash, 1977; Volume #: 1, Issue #: 1; 11.5x15 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    Editors: Steven Samiof, Melanie Nissen
    Notes: For Slash, see also New York Rocker #42
  - Slash, 1977; Volume #: 1, Issue #: 2; 11.5x15 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Slash, 1977; Volume #: 1, Issue #: 3; 11.5x15 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Slash, 1977; Volume #: 1, Issue #: 4; 11.5x15 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Slash, 1977; Volume #: 1, Issue #: 5; 11.5x15 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Slash, 1977; Volume #: 1, Issue #: 6; 11.5x15 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Slash, 1978; Volume #: 1, Issue #: 7; 11.5x15 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Slash, 1978; Volume #: 1, Issue #: 8; 11.5x15 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Slash, 1978; Volume #: 1, Issue #: 9; 11.5x15 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Slash, 1978; Volume #: 1, Issue #: 10; 11.5x15 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Slash, 1978; Volume #: 1, Issue #: 11; 11.5x15 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Slash, 1978; Volume #: 1, Issue #: 12; 11.5x15 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Slash, 1978; Volume #: 2, Issue #: 1; 11.5x15 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Slash, 1978; Volume #: 2, Issue #: 2; 11.5x15 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Slash, 1979; Volume #: 2, Issue #: 3; 11.5x15 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Slash, 1979; Volume #: 2, Issue #: 4; 11.5x15 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Slash, 1979; Volume #: 2, Issue #: 5; 11.5x15 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Slash, 1979; Volume #: 2, Issue #: 6; 11.5x15 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Slash, 1979; Volume #: 2, Issue #: 7; 11.5x15 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Slash, 1979; Volume #: 2, Issue #: 8; 11.5x15 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Slash, 1979; Volume #: 2, Issue #: 9; 11.5x15 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Slash, 1979; Volume #: 2, Issue #: 10; 11.5x15 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Slash, 1979; Volume #: 2, Issue #: 11; 11.5x15 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Editors: Claude Bessy, Philomena
  - Slash, 1980; Volume #: 3, Issue #: 1; 11.5x15 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Slash, 1980; Volume #: 3, Issue #: 2; 11.5x15 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Slash, April, 1980; Volume #: 3, Issue #: 3; 11.5x15 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Slash, 1980; Volume #: 3, Issue #: 4; 11.5x15 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Slash, 1980; Volume #: 3, Issue #: 5; 11.5x15 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Editors: Claude Bessy, Chris D.
  - Slash, 1978-06; Issue #: Free giveaway issue; 11.5x15 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Sounds, March 4, 1977; 43 x 30 cm. (Box 18, Folder 3)
    Notes: Johnny Rotten cover story
  - Sounds, February 10, 1979; 43 x 30 cm. (Box 18, Folder 3)
    Notes: DIY reviews
  - Sounds, February 17, 1979; 43 x 30 cm. (Box 18, Folder 3)
    Notes: No Wave, Pere Ubu articles
  - Sounds, March 3, 1979; 43 x 30 cm. (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Sounds, March 31, 1979; 43 x 30 cm. (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Sounds, April 28, 1979; 43 x 30 cm. (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Sounds, May 5, 1979; 43 x 30 cm. (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Sounds, May 26, 1979; 43 x 30 cm. (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Notes: DIY reviews, Swell Maps
  - Sounds, June 9, 1979; 43 x 30 cm. (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Notes: Cramps article
  - Sounds, August 25, 1979; 43 x 30 cm. (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Notes: Bill Drummond article
  - Sounds, September 29, 1979; 43 x 30 cm. (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Sounds, October 6, 1979; 43 x 30 cm. (Box 19, Folder 2)
    Notes: Ian Dury family tree
  - Sounds, November 10, 1979; 43 x 30 cm. (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Sounds, December 1, 1979; 43 x 30 cm. (Box 19, Folder 3)
    Notes: Wavis O'Shave
  - Sounds, December 15, 1979; 43 x 30 cm. (Box 19, Folder 3)
    Notes: Throbbig Gristle, Wavis O'Shave coverage
  - Sounds, January 26, 1980; 43 x 30 cm. (Box 19, Folder 3)
    Notes: Wavis O'Shave, Metabolist review
  - Sounds, March 8, 1980; 43 x 30 cm. (Box 19, Folder 4)
    Notes: Cabaret Voltaire, Absurd records
  - Sounds, March 22, 1980; 43 x 30 cm. (Box 19, Folder 4)
    Notes: Cramps interview
  - Sounds, May 3, 1980; 43 x 30 cm. (Box 19, Folder 4)
    Notes: Desperate Bicycles review
  - Sounds, May 10, 1980; 43 x 30 cm. (Box 19, Folder 5)
    Notes: Scissor Fits
  - Sounds, June 7, 1980; 43 x 30 cm. (Box 19, Folder 5)
    Notes: DIY record guide
  - Sounds, June 21, 1980; 43 x 30 cm. (Box 20, Folder 1)
    Notes: DIY record reviews, punk clothes feature
  - Sounds, June 28, 1980; 43 x 30 cm. (Box 20, Folder 1)
    Notes: DIY record corner, Fuck Off Records
  - Sounds, July 12, 1980; 43 x 30 cm. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Sounds, July 19, 1980; 43 x 30 cm. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Sounds, July 26, 1980; 43 x 30 cm. (Box 20, Folder 2)
    Notes: DIY reviews, Malcolm McLaren article
  - Sounds, August 2, 1980; 43 x 30 cm. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Sounds, August 16, 1980; 43 x 30 cm. (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Sounds, August 23, 1980; 43 x 30 cm. (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Sounds, August 30, 1980; 43 x 30 cm. (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Sounds, September 6, 1980; 43 x 30 cm. (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Sounds, September 20, 1980; 43 x 30 cm. (Box 20, Folder 4)
    Notes: DIY reviews, Ferrets review
  - Sounds, September 27, 1980; 43 x 30 cm. (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Sounds, October 4, 1980; 43 x 30 cm. (Box 20, Folder 5)
    Notes: Lemon Kittens, Androids of Mu review
  - Sounds, 1980; 43 x 30 cm. (Box 21, Folder 1)
    Notes: DIY reviews, Industrial feature
  - Sounds, 1980; 43 x 30 cm. (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Sounds, 1980; 43 x 30 cm. (Box 21, Folder 1)
    Notes: Androids of Mu
  - Sounds, 1980; 43 x 30 cm. (Box 21, Folder 2)
    Notes: DIY corner, punk fashion ads
  - Sounds, 1980; 43 x 30 cm. (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Sounds, 1980; 43 x 30 cm. (Box 21, Folder 2)
    Notes: Fanzine reviews
  - Sounds, 1980; 43 x 30 cm. (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Sounds, 1980; 43 x 30 cm. (Box 21, Folder 3)
    Notes: DIY reviews, Lemon Kittens
  - Sounds, 1980; 43 x 30 cm. (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Sounds (U.S.), 1977; Issue #: 54; 11x14.5 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    Publication location: Phoenix, AZ, United States
    Notes: New Wave cover story. Grelun Landon (addressed to)
  - Spurt, 1978; Issue #: 5/6; 11x17 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    Notes: Continues as No Magazine
  - Stelazine, 1978; Volume #: 2, Issue #: 2; 11.5x16.5 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Street Life (UK), 1975; Volume #: 2, Issue #: 1; 16 x 12 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    Editors: Billy Walker
  - Substitute, 1978; Issue #: 2; 17 x 11.5 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Take It!, 1981; Issue #: 1; 11x16 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    Editors: Michael Koenig
    Notes: Numbering is idiosyncratic: This issue numbered "Premier" (i.e. 1). Flexidisc lacking.
  - Take It!, 1981; Issue #: [2]; 11x16 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    Notes: Numbering is idiosyncratic: This issue numbered "B" (i.e. 2). Flexidisc lacking.
  - Take It!, 1981; Issue #: [3]; 11x16 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    Notes: Numbering is idiosyncratic: This issue numbered "3rd Eye" (i.e. 3). Flexidisc lacking.
  - Take It!, 1981; Issue #: [4]; 11x16 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    Notes: Numbering is idiosyncratic: This issue numbered "Grand Slam" (i.e. 4). Flexidisc lacking.
  - Take It!, 1982; Issue #: [5]; 11x16 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    Notes: Numbering is idiosyncratic: This issue numbered "Five Star" (i.e. 5). Flexidisc lacking.
  - Thunder Road, 1978; Volume #: 1, Issue #: 1; 17 x 11 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    Publication location: Cypress, CA, United States
    Editors: Lou Cohan, Ken Viola
  - Today, 1978; 60 x 37 cm., folded to 37 x 30 cm. (Box 22, Folder 5)
    Publication location: [New York], United States
    Notes: Lead story: Sid Vicious arrest for murder of Nancy Spungeon
  - Travelers Digest, 1978-Spring; Volume #: 1, Issue #: 3; 14 x 11 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    Editors: Jeff Goldberg
  - Trick, 1977; Issue #: 1; 17x12 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Trick, 1977; Issue #: 2; 17x12 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Village Cry, 1977; Issue #: 6; 15.5 x 11 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    Publication location: Basel, Switzerland
    Editors: Beat Presser
  - Village Voice, March 5, 1976; Volume #: 21, Issue #: 9; 15.5 x 11 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    Notes: Cover story on Lou Reed and punk
  - Village Voice, 1977; Volume #: 22, Issue #: 13; 15.5 x 11 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    Major contributors: Mary Harron
    Notes: "Special 24-page section: British Rock Lives". Pages 50-78 only, comprising the special section on British rock (including a section on punk by Mary Harron).
  - Village Voice, October 24, 1977; 15.5 x 11 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    Notes: "Special section: Avant-Punk". Pages 57-80 only, comprising a special section on punk.
  - White Noise (CA), 1977; Issue #: Free Sample Issue; 15 x 11.5 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    Editors: Gene Sculatti, Ronn Spencer
  - White Noise (MI), 1978?; Issue #: 1; 15 x 11.5 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    Publication location: Northville, MI, United States
    Editors: Jerry Vile, Paul Stillborn (Paul F. Zimmerman)
  - White Noise (MI), 1978?; Issue #: 3; 15 x 11.5 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    Editors: Jerry Vile, Paul Ginsuknife (Paul F. Zimmerman)
  - White Noise (MI), 1979?; Issue #: 4; 15 x 11.5 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    Editors: Paul X (Paul F. Zimmerman)
  - White Noise (MI), 1979; Issue #: 5; 15 x 11.5 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Series IV. Ephemera
  - Subseries IVa. Press Kits, Band Publicity, Etc.
    - John Cale press packet containing 13 articles, ca. 1977 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Mabuhay Gardens collection of 10 record charts, 1978-1979.3. (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Television press packet, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Bomp! Set sale list no. 20, 1974-1979 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Sex Pistols Bomp! File (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Sex Pistols sales conference poster (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Rough Trade archive (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Mixed Media Montages (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - CBGB's concert bill, December 1977 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Goodwin, Michael. "Music Gonna Shock you Like Electric: A City Guite to Reggae Records", ca. 1970s (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - New York Dolls/The Stooges Private Party invitation, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Generation X press release declaring they have been recruited to boot camp, February 11, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 1)